<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<Loop_ZDreamerAloneO>You think about your questions.</Loop_ZDreamerAloneO>

<GoToMain_ZDreamer>...what's the deal with those strange walls outside?</GoToMain_ZDreamer>

<QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerAlone>...what's the story behind peg legs?</QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerAlone>
<QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerAloneO>"There's not much to say, really," says {Interviewee_nameDef} massaging {Interviewee_possessive} side. "Doctors at the clinic did a really good job. No accidental cuts, no phantom pain. Very neat. I needed money, you see. This is how I built this place."
\n\n{Interviewee_pronoun} must have been very desperate, since organic limbs don't sell for that much. You wonder how did {Interviewee_pronoun} survive on such a meager payout. Seeing your expression {Interviewee_nameDef} sighs deeply as if {Interviewee_pronoun} was giving up {Interviewee_possessive} last breath.
\n\n"All the money's gone now," {Interviewee_pronoun} says, looking you straight in the eye and clenching {Interviewee_possessive} fists on the haft of {Interviewee_possessive} breach axe. "I've got nothing left except for my walls. And just so you know {Interviewer_nameDef}, I won't let anyone to knock them down."
\n\nSomehow you doubt that. Maybe because of {Interviewee_possessive} general state or maybe because of the immense exhaustion in {Interviewee_nameDef}'s eyes.
\n\n</QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerAloneO>
<LoopBack_ZDreamerAlone>Ask about something else.</LoopBack_ZDreamerAlone>

<QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerAlone>...why would you live alone?</QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerAlone>
<QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerAloneO>"I don't need other people and other people don't need me," says {Interviewee_nameDef}.
\n\nThen {Interviewee_pronoun} looks away and falls silent.
\n\nTime passes. {Interviewee_pronoun}'s still looking away and still keeping silent.
\n\nYou guess {Interviewee_pronoun} has made {Interviewee_pronoun} point.
\n\n</QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerAloneO>

<QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerAlone>...why does the only torch here stand in the farthest corner?</QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerAlone>
<QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerAloneO>"I like it there," says {Interviewee_nameDef}.
\n\nOh no, you didn't ask this question to be satisfied with such a lousy answer. This setup is far too unusual to simply ignore. Stone floor and stone walls, while the rest of the house is built of wood? (Granite door jambs don't count; their purpose is to fortify the enterance). And what about that barrel? Is it full of water? Is {Interviewee_pronoun} afraid a torch could... start a fire? That's a ridiculous idea, but Shifts happen and the next one could be about torches and campfires igniting everything around them.
\n\nYou launch a barrage of questions at {Interviewee_nameDef}. {Interviewee_pronoun} knows something!
\n\n"Look, it's nothing. This is how people build where I'm from."
\n\n{Interviewee_pronoun} refuses to tell you where {Interviewee_pronoun}'s from and whether {Interviewee_possessive} people are still alive. In fact, {Interviewee_pronoun} refuses to talk to you at all. But you notice {Interviewee_objective} giving the stony corner an uneasy, sideways look.
\n\nThe torch sputters ominously.
\n\n</QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerAloneO>

<QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerAlone>...is it true thrumbos can speak? (Now the thought is in your head)</QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerAlone>
<QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerAloneO>"I guess I asked for this," {Interviewee_nameDef} shakes {Interviewee_possessive} head. "Yes, I think they can speak. But one needs to earn their trust and I'm sure they would never say a word to someone who tamed and killed one of their kind. That's a single most rotten thing a person can do, if you ask me."
\n\n"Please {Interviewer_nameDef}, don't ask me," {Interviewee_pronoun} adds quickly. "No more random questions, all right?"</QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerAloneO>

<QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerAlone>...you don't really feel like answering my questions, do you?</QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerAlone>
<QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerAloneO>"No," says {Interviewee_nameDef}.
\n\nAnd that's that. Well, at least {Interviewee_pronoun}'s honest.</QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerAloneO>

</LanguageData>