<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<Loop_ZDreamerRecruitedO>You might have a few questions to ask.</Loop_ZDreamerRecruitedO>

<QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerRecruited>...do you feel like answering some questions now?</QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerRecruited>
<QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerRecruitedO>"Ask me {Interviewer_nameDef} and see for yourself," says {Interviewee_nameDef} with a smile.</QuestionCrappyAnswers_ZDreamerRecruitedO>
<LoopBack_ZDreamerRecruited>Talk about something else.</LoopBack_ZDreamerRecruited>

<QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerRecruited>...what's the story behind peg legs?</QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerRecruited>
<QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerRecruitedO>"I sold the originals. And a kidney too," says {Interviewee_nameDef} patting {Interviewee_possessive} side. "You know how shitty deconstruction is. I was building and knocking my walls down, burning plasteel like wood. I needed all the money I could get." You wonder what's the full story, since organic limbs don't sell for that much. {Interviewee_pronoun} reads your expression and clicks {Interviewee_possessive} tongue.
\n\n"Remember when Potozky announced his brand new trading system?" You nod your head. You're not sure about that particular event, but Potozky and his powerful VE Corp came up with more projects than you could count.
\n\n"Another Shift was in the air and when it happened, the system went live. It was brilliant at first. Prices fluctuated all over the region and long distance trading was suddenly worth it. But then the usual tweakery started and everything went to hell. Fortunes were made and lost in blink of an eye! Flesh prices in the nearest town skyrocketed and I jumped at the opportunity."
\n\n"Speaking of jumping, do you recon you could afford a pair of decent bionics for your new recruit?" {Interviewee_nameDef} asks with a twinkle in {Interviewee_possessive} eye. You make a noncommittal grunt and wave at {Interviewee_objective} to continue.
\n\n"Anyway. I cashed in and bolted as the place turned... ulgy. Doctors at the clinic did a really good job. No accidental cuts, no phantom pain. I could move and fight without a problem after I finished throwing up. Still, it's not an easy thing to be rid of your own two legs. But I didn't do it just for the money."
\n\n"The thing is, Potozky didn't create that overhaul by himself. He partnered up with a legend. None other than Taran Chuk, one of the three madmen who once tried to achieve Z Levels. And now Taran Chuk was involved in a project that made my flesh worth thousands. It was like a sign, a call to prove my commitment. I was foolish of course, foolish beyond words." {Interviewee_nameDef} sighs deeply, but there's a smile on {Interviewee_possessive} lips.
\n\n</QuestionWhyNoLegs_ZDreamerRecruitedO>

<QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerRecruited>...why would you live alone?</QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerRecruited>
<QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerRecruitedO>"I'm surprised you need to ask after listening to my story," says {Interviewee_nameDef}. "When people of my settlement understood what I was about, they stripped me naked and kicked me out. After I got the same treatment at the next place, I tried to be smart and kept my mouth shut. It was no use. My work was too costly, too useless to fund."
\n\n"So I ended up on the road, taking odd jobs and hunting for prescious deposits. It was a rough life and I couldn't make any progress. Then another Shift brought me my lucky break." {Interviewee_pronoun} pats {Interviewee_possessive} peg leg smiling wistfully. "I built this place and devoted everything to my project."
\n\n"Did I miss other people? Sometimes, yes. But my obsession kept me going. When I finally realised Z Levels were beyond my ability, I felt like... like I reached the end of the line. I had nothing to strive for, nothing to live for."
\n\n"Thank you {Interviewee_nameDef} for changing that."
\n\n</QuestionWhyNoFamily_ZDreamerRecruitedO>

<QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerRecruited>...why does the only torch here stand in the farthest corner?</QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerRecruited>
<QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerRecruitedO>"You leave no stone unturned, do you {Interviewer_nameDef}?" laughs {Interviewee_nameDef}. "You know there are disturbed people on this planet, people who relish in the suffering of others. One of them created a project that made torches and campfires ignite flammables around them. I never experienced it first hand, but I've seen my parents' burn scars."
\n\nYou want to know the name of this sick individual.
\n\n"I don't believe in that supersitious Beyonders-are-listening crap but... Hell! Maybe I do, in this case. I'm not going to say their name. And I hope that when the world moves on their Ignition project is buried and forgotten. This is why I love plasteel so much. Unlike shitty steel it's immune to fire."
\n\nYou agree with {Interviewee_objective} wholeheartedly but...
\n\n"...that corner looks kind of nice, doesn't it? Like there was a bit more care, bit more thinking behind usual planning. I must say I enjoyed fixing that little stone curb. I tell you, colony built with fire safety in mind is very pleasing to the eye. Especially when people are not afraid to challenge the Triad and combine stone with wood." {Interviewee_nameDef} proudly lifts {Interviewer_possessive} head.
\n\nThe candle on the reasearch bench makes a tiny crackling sound, drawing your attention. A moth has flown into a flame and was burned into a crisp.
\n\nCandle. Flame. Wooden research bench.
\n\n{Interviewee_nameDef} puts a finger to {Interviewee_possessive} lips and you quickly change the subject.
\n\n</QuestionCornerTorch_ZDreamerRecruitedO>

<QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerRecruited>...is it true thrumbos can speak? (The thought is still in your head)</QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerRecruited>
<QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerRecruitedO>"Oh, I'm sure they can speak. Have you ever heard the sound they make when they are hurt? When they die?" {Interviewee_nameDef}'s face contorts in pain. "You can almost make out words, it's heartbreaking. They are the kindest creatures on the rim and maybe the rest of us is just too damn cruel to hear them speak."
\n\n"There's this story I heard long time ago. Another trio of crashlanded people, another colony. Completely clueless, had no idea what they were doing. So afraid, they kept building spike traps all over the perimeter and had to sleep on the floor. A few caravans arrived, made some sweet deals and left without a single word of advice. That colony was doomed to fail."
\n\n"And then a single thrumbo turned up. The animal guy approached it with a stupid smile on his face and... tamed it just like that!" {Interviewee_pronoun} flicks {Interviewee_possessive} fingers. "Tamed? More like that thrumbo joined them out of pity. Bastards kept sending the poor thing against every threat and with barely any support. In the end, shotguns and maces brought it down for good. Colony followed soon after."
\n\n"What I'm trying to say is maybe it's not just about cruelty. Maybe we're too selfish for thrumbos to talk with us..." {Interviewee_nameDef} suddenly lights up. "What if this is why they keep wandering in and out of settlements? Because they are looking, endlessly looking for someone who's worthy?"
\n\nThat's an interesting theory, but you have more questions. What does {Interviewee_pronoun} know about a mythical gallatross?
\n\n{Interviewee_nameDef} groans. "Please {Interviewer_nameDef}, enough!"
\n\n</QuestionTalkingThrumbos_ZDreamerRecruitedO>
<Rat3_ZDreamer>Let's deal with the talking rat once and for all.</Rat3_ZDreamer>
<Rat3_ZDreamerDreamsO>"Yes," says {Interviewee_nameDef}. You look at {Interviewee_objective} with surprise since you said nothing yet.
\n\n"You asked about thrumbos, so I figured another rat question was incoming. The answer is yes. I've run into a talking rat in my outhouse."
\n\nAll this time you were being shamelessly gaslighted! And by someone who values honesty above all. You demand a thorough explanation.
\n\n"What can I say? A few years back I decided to tidy up the place and a talking rat jumped out, offering to share its wisdom. I run away and it must've slipped out after me. I was afraid I was losing my mind. But now, after listening to you... Hell, I believe in talking thrumbos, so talking rats aren't that much of a stretch!"
\n\nYou're happy that {Interviewee_pronoun}'s made peace with the maddness of this world but it's a shame the two of you lost a chance to partake in the wisdom of a rat sage.
\n\n"Maybe we did, or maybe we didn't?" Says {Interviewee_nameDef} with a smile on {Interviewee_possessive} face. "Maybe there's one last rat sage in these parts?"
\n\n</Rat3_ZDreamerDreamsO>

<!-- CQF doesn't allow for more than one conditional hediff. Option suspended for now.
<Rat3_ZDreamerWakesO>"No," says {Interviewee_nameDef}. You look at {Interviewee_objective} with surprise since you said nothing yet.
\n\n"You asked about thrumbos, so I figured another rat question was incoming. The answer is no. There are no talking rats here or anywhere else."
\n\nThere's absolute conviction written all over {Interviewee_nameDef}'s face. You conceal a sigh of relief. Everything's all right with the world and with you.</Rat3_ZDreamerWakesO> -->

<DreamerDreamsOnNewVision_ZDreamer>Those walls are your legacy. We cannot destroy them. (Recruit and move on)</DreamerDreamsOnNewVision_ZDreamer>
<DreamerDreamsOnNewVision_ZDreamerO>\n\nYou're about to get going, but {Interviewee_nameDef} has one last thing to say.
\n\n"Maybe we already talked about it, but I think you should walk around western clump of walls. You might experience something interesting. Down to earth person would not enjoy it, but you're not down to earth, are you {Interviewer_nameDef}?"
\n\nAre you flattered? You suppose you should feel flattered.
\n\n"Just don't do anything crazy. Focus on what's before you and you should be fine. You and I, both of us will be fine," adds {Interviewee_nameDef}.
\n\nYou could investigate, but everyone has a right to remain cryptic. From time to time, that is. And if you don't feel like walking around some strange plasteel walls, then... don't.</DreamerDreamsOnNewVision_ZDreamerO>
<DreamerDreamsOnWallsUp_ZDreamer>Let's move out!</DreamerDreamsOnWallsUp_ZDreamer>

<DreamerDreamsOnWallsDown_ZDreamer>Plasteel's always in short supply. Thank you, friend. (Recruit and move on)</DreamerDreamsOnWallsDown_ZDreamer>

<DreamerWakesUpWallsDown_ZDreamer>Let's put that axe of yours to work. (Recruit and move on)</DreamerWakesUpWallsDown_ZDreamer>

<DreamerIgnored2_ZDreamer>On second thought, you decide to leave alone. (Don't recruit, move on)</DreamerIgnored2_ZDreamer>

</LanguageData>