<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<SecretLoop_ZDreamerO>You are still alive. You can breathe in and out, your blood is not boiling and your mind is your own. At least for now. Plasteel under your feet feels as solid and reliable as it should, but everywhere else stretches only infinite... strangeness. Almost everywhere. Something red and terrible looms up in the north. 
\n\nThere are a few more familiar spots: plasteel tiles to the east of you. Inaccessible due to their awkward placement, they form a U-shaped pattern. You've seen it before, haven't you? A footprint of those strange plasteel walls would look exactly the same. Does it mean you travelled - climbed - up and are now standing on top of a wall block?
\n\nAs ridiculous as it sounds, that seems to be the gist of it. This is no place for any laws-of-physics-abiding creature, and yet here you are.
\n\nYour attention is being drawn to the thing in front of you, a bluish-glowing anomaly. Ignore it! Ignore it and run from this hellish place while you still can!
\n\n</SecretLoop_ZDreamerO>
<CheckWayDown_ZDreamer>Make sure the way out is open.</CheckWayDown_ZDreamer>
<Anomaly_ZDreamer>Focus on the anomaly.</Anomaly_ZDreamer>
<AbyssLookOrNot_ZDreamer>Look the red abyss instead.</AbyssLookOrNot_ZDreamer>
<LeaveSecret_ZDreamer>Leave.</LeaveSecret_ZDreamer>

<CheckWayDown_ZDreamerO>Looking down makes you queasy, as if you were in a drop pod arcing down towards the ground. Pay more attention to the surface at your feet and you will simply slide down, back into the world you know. Probably.
\n\nAn abstract, and yet somewhat interesting question forms in your mind. What would happen to you if someone - or something - were to destroy any of the walls the tops of which you are currently seeing? Your survival instinct gives you a quick and direct answer.
\n\nYou would be trapped here forever.
\n\n</CheckWayDown_ZDreamerO>
<LoopBack_ZDreamerSecret>Continue.</LoopBack_ZDreamerSecret>

<Anomaly_ZDreamerO>Driven by what might be a suicidal curiousity, you look closer at the thing before you.
\n\nAt first is seems like a floating sphere, covered in thousands of head-sized bumps, its texture that of granite. It's drawing your gaze with the force of a powerful magnet pulling tiny bits of steel. That's what your eyes are, two helpless globes of steel rolling out of your skull and down into maddness.
\n\nIs this really happening?!
\n\nThis is exactly what's happening. The sphere morphs into a column, a column rising from some impossible dimension, a black hole that's sucking in your sense of sight. And your sanity.
\n\n</Anomaly_ZDreamerO>

<AnomalyDreamerNo_ZDreamer>Tear your eyes away before it's too late!</AnomalyDreamerNo_ZDreamer>
<AnomalyDreamerNo_ZDreamerO>With every fibre of your being, with every bit of your willpower you pull, and pull your senses back into yourself!
\n\nYou quickly turn away from the anomaly and take stock. Something's wrong, very wrong. Your eyesight feels weak. Like worn out hands too tired to grasp anything, your perception slips from your fingers you're trying to count. A realization strikes you: you yourself have no idea how many fingers you're holding up.
\n\nNot just eyes then. Your brain got hit as well.
\n\nAt least your brain is not damaged so bad as not to know it's been damaged in first place.</AnomalyDreamerNo_ZDreamerO>
<AnomalyDreamerNoEnd_ZDreamer>You stumble away from this hellish place.</AnomalyDreamerNoEnd_ZDreamer>

<AnomalyDreamerYes_ZDreamer>Fall, fall down and let your mind follow your perception.</AnomalyDreamerYes_ZDreamer>
<AnomalyDreamerYes_ZDreamerO>The sensation of losing your sight is deeply unsettling, but you refuse to give in to fear.
\n\nYou are not leaping blindly into the dark - you know somewhere out there is a shadow of what could be. A fleeting vision of a world so different and yet so familiar. High walls with walkways, overlooking plains and forests on one side and bustling settlements on the other. Multi storey houses, towers, networks of underground tunnels linking bases with fortified outposts. And deeper still, mine shafts plumbing darkness, corridors and halls like glowing roots, spreading light where no light belongs.
\n\nInstead of crumbling, your consciousness expands. What you're seeing is too grand, too complex to comprehend but the core idea of it is crystal clear. For a moment you hold it in your mind, a dream come true. And then, like a dream, it is gone.
\n\nBut not without a trace. A shadow of shadow remains, for you to carry away from this place and to keep as long as you live.
\n\n</AnomalyDreamerYes_ZDreamerO>
<AnomalyDreamerYesEnd_ZDreamer>You step back, overwhelmed by wonder.</AnomalyDreamerYesEnd_ZDreamer>

<AbyssLookOrNot_ZDreamerO>A piece of half-remembered folk wisdom floats into your mind, something about dangers of doing what you're about to do. This might be a really bad idea. Are you sure you want to proceed?</AbyssLookOrNot_ZDreamerO>
<AbyssLookYes_ZDreamer>Yes, you boldly gaze into the unknown.</AbyssLookYes_ZDreamer>
<AbyssLookNo_ZDreamer>No, you wisely avert your eyes.</AbyssLookNo_ZDreamer>

</LanguageData>