<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<Intro_ZDreamerO>"Greetings stranger. I appreciate you didn't try to tear down my life's work without talking to me first." {Interviewee_pronoun} looks at you, smiling weakly. In {Interviewee_possessive} calloused hands {Interviewee_pronoun} tightly grips a massive breach axe. {Interviewee_possessive} legs were replaced by crude wooden pegs and, judging by the state of the wood, it happened long time ago.
\n\n"My name's {Interviewee_nameFull} of the End of the Line."
\n\n</Intro_ZDreamerO>
<EndLineInt3Dwn_ZDreamer>What a strange faction name! You introduce yourself.</EndLineInt3Dwn_ZDreamer>
<EndLineInt3Up_ZDreamer>This planet breaks people. You introduce yourself.</EndLineInt3Up_ZDreamer>

<Rat1_ZDreamer>Share your conversation with the illusory talking rat.</Rat1_ZDreamer>
<Rat1_ZDreamerO>{Interviewee_nameDef} looks at you cautiously.
\n\n"You cleaned my outhouse before talking to me?"
\n\nYou wave the question away. {Interviewee_pronoun}'s focusing on unimportant details.
\n\n"No, I've never met a talking rat inside or outside of an outhouse, or any house for that matter. But carry on believing whatever you like."
\n\n{Interviewee_pronoun}'s missing the point again. You're not saying there WAS a talking rat. Only that your hallucination of such a rat was very vivid and almost too convincing. Seeing {Interviewee_nameDef}'s expression you sigh and break mid-sentence.
\n\nMaybe another opportunity to discuss this subject will present itself later on.
\n\n</Rat1_ZDreamerO>
<Rat1Back_ZDreamer>Go be a reasonable person again.</Rat1Back_ZDreamer>

<EndLineInt3Dwn_ZDreamerO>{Interviewee_nameDef} chuckles at your confusion.
\n\n"What I meant is that I'm on my own. I've got no friends or family, not any more," {Interviewee_pronoun} clears {Interviewee_possessive} throat. "Anyway. I'm glad to make your acquaintance, {Interviewer_nameFull} of {Interviewer_factionName}. I welcome you at my table and my food is your food. Are you hungry?"
\n\nYou can't help but notice {Interviewee_nameDef}'s sunken cheeks and slumped shoulders. You don't think {Interviewee_pronoun}'s been eating enough recently.
\n\n</EndLineInt3Dwn_ZDreamerO>
<DontGimmeFood_ZDreamer>Refuse politely. You cannot accept food from someone who's malnourished.</DontGimmeFood_ZDreamer>
<GimmeFood_ZDreamer>You never say no to a free meal.</GimmeFood_ZDreamer>
<GiveThemFoodSurvival_ZDreamer>No, you are the one who's going to share. (Give a survival meal)</GiveThemFoodSurvival_ZDreamer>
<GiveThemFoodPemmican_ZDreamer>No, you are the one who's going to share. (Give some pemmican)</GiveThemFoodPemmican_ZDreamer>

<EndLineInt3Up_ZDreamerO>That's unexpected. It looks like {Interviewee_nameDef} is really on {Interviewee_possessive} own. Most people would do anything they could to hide such weakness.
\n\n"I'm glad to make your acquaintance, {Interviewer_nameFull} of {Interviewer_factionName}. I welcome you at my table. My food is your food. Are you hungry?"
\n\nYou can't help but notice {Interviewee_nameDef}'s sunken cheeks and slumped shoulders. You don't think {Interviewee_pronoun}'s been eating enough recently.
\n\n</EndLineInt3Up_ZDreamerO>

<DontGimmeFood_ZDreamerO>{Interviewee_nameDef} nods {Interviewee_possessive} head.
\n\n"As you wish, {Interviewer_nameDef}. I'm sure you have some questions. Not many people dare to travel so you deserve at least a few answers for your efforts. Just remember, this place is the end of the line. There's not much to say about anything here. Myself included."
\n\n</DontGimmeFood_ZDreamerO>
<GimmeFood_ZDreamerO>Without looking, {Interviewee_nameDef} points at the wooden shelf with a lone survival meal on it. You'll grab it after you are done talking. Keeping good manners is important.
\n\nOf course it is possible you've already helped yourself to it. Not very well-mannered if you did, but the host doesn't seem to care.
\n\n"I'm sure you have some questions, {Interviewer_nameDef}. Not many people dare to travel, so you deserve at least a few answers for your efforts. Ask away. Mind you, I don't have much to say."
\n\n</GimmeFood_ZDreamerO>
<GiveThemFood_ZDreamerO>There's another shadow of a smile on {Interviewee_nameDef}'s face.
\n\n"You're too kind for your own good, {Interviewer_nameDef}. But then if more people where like you, this planet would be better off. I will gladly share meal with you after we're done talking."
\n\n{Interviewee_pronoun} speaks the words, but they sound hollow to you. There's no heart behind them. {Interviewee_pronoun} doesn't seem dishonest, simply... lifeless.
\n\n"You look like someone who lives to poke and prod everything around you," {Interviewee_nameDef} makes a weary gesture as if waving {Interviewee_possessive} own words away. "I mean no offence. That's a good thing, this is how people move forward. But you won't find any progress here, {Interviewer_nameDef}. So ask me whatever you want to ask and let's have something to eat."
\n\n</GiveThemFood_ZDreamerO>

<IntroEnd_ZDreamer>Curiosity killed a cat. Good thing you're not a cat.</IntroEnd_ZDreamer>

</LanguageData>